[train whistle blaring]
[Triste] It's too much for me. You try.
[José Arcadio II]
It's impossible like that.
- [Triste] Come on.
- It's impossible.
- Good night.
- See you soon. cousin.
- I'll let you win next time. all right?
- And gotta practice.
Hello.
Hey.
[unsettling music playing]
[man] Aureliano.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[man] Aureliano.
- [gunshot]
- No!
[woman breathes shakily]
[sobs] No!
[man] Aureliano.
- [gunshot]
- [clucking]
[bell tolls]
Aureliano.
[music fades]
[narrator] Over the course
of a single week.
all 17 Aurelianos
were hunted down like rabbits
by invisible criminals… who killed them.
taking aim at the ash crosses
on their foreheads.
[melancholy music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
Those bastards got to Centeno too.
[Úrsula] My God.
Who could have done this?
[José Arcadio II]
No one in Macondo saw anything.
There are no witnesses anywhere.
[Aureliano] Witnesses?
Are you serious. José Arcadio?
You're telling me
you need someone to confirm
that your bosses did this
with the help of the government?
No.
[Aureliano] Who branded their foreheads
like they were cattle?
Hmm?
Let's go.
[Aureliano] Gerineldo.
We're going to show
those gringo motherfuckers
that they are not the ones
in charge in Colombia.
You understand?
- Aureliano.
- Hmm?
I knew age had caught up with you.
but not this much.
I'm terribly sorry. my friend.
but someone had to say it.
[Aureliano] Hmm.
Grieving is the only thing left
for you to do now.
[Aureliano] Mm-hmm.
[grunts]
[groans]
[breathing heavily]
If you've come here to defend them.
get the fuck out.
I was the last person to see Triste alive.
And I'm gonna keep asking questions
because someone's gotta pay for this.
The only one who's paying here is me.
And that's exactly what they want.
[dark ethereal music playing]
You know. maybe I deserved it.
No one deserves to suffer like this.
You never understood war.
Leave me alone.
[narrator] Just as during the war.
after the deaths of his dearest friends.
the colonel felt no sorrow.
but rather a blind and directionless rage.
An exhausting helplessness.
He was lost…
adrift in a strange house
where nothing and no one
evoked the slightest hint of affection.
[laughter echoes]
[narrator] The air was filled
with the unbearable stench
of rotten memories.
[lively music plays]
[dark ethereal music continues]
[narrator] It was on October 11th.
at ten minutes past four.
that for the first time since his youth.
the colonel knowingly stepped
into a trap of nostalgia…
[elephant trumpets]
…as he relived the wondrous afternoon
when his father took him to discover ice.
[wistful music playing]
[footsteps thumping]
[elephant trumpets]
[wistful music continues]
[music fades]
[narrator] And when it was all over.
he found himself face-to-face
with his miserable solitude once again.
So he walked over to the chestnut tree.
with the circus still on his mind.
[melancholy music playing]
[urine splashing]
Mm…
[narrator] He tried to keep thinking
about the circus while he urinated…
but could no longer find memory of it.
[groaning]
[grunts. groans]
[melancholy music continues]
[music fades]
[Úrsula sniffles]
[melancholy music resumes]
You have found rest at last. my child.
[sniffles]
[Úrsula sobs]
ONE HUNDRED YEARS OF SOLITUDE
[indistinct chattering]
[narrator] Years later.
nobody in Macondo remembered the colonel.
IN MEMORY OF COLONEL AURELIANO BUENDÍA
RELENTLESS DEFENDER OF FREEDOM AND JUSTICE
HIS FIGHT FOR A SOVEREIGN NATION
WILL LIVE ON IN THE HEART OF HIS PEOPLE
- [people clamoring]
- [mysterious music playing]
[narrator] Aureliano Segundo
had become fat. violet. and tortoise-like.
the result of an appetite
comparable only to José Arcadio's
when he returned
from his trip around the world.
And he became the undefeated champion
of the absurd eating contests
of endurance and gluttony.
held at Petra Cotes's house.
Until one unfortunate Saturday
when Camila Sagastume showed up.
"Dearest Mother."
"Nothing brings me more joy
than reading in your letters
how happy you and Father are."
[young Meme] As for me.
I have wonderful news to share with you.
My graduation as a clavichord soloist
is set for the end of this month…
[clamoring continues]
…so it won't be long
before I return to Macondo for good.
[clamoring continues]
And nothing thrills me more
than the thought of
living with the family again.
[man] Come on. you can do it!
[music fades]
[Aureliano II groans]
Fernanda.
[young Meme] See you soon. your daughter.
Renata.
[door opens]
[Aureliano II groaning]
[man] That's it.
[labored breathing]
[man] Ms. Petra sent you this.
- [softly] Aureliano.
- Yeah. yeah. yeah.
Aureliano.
[bell ringing]
Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah.
Aureliano. don't do this.
[somber music playing]
[rooster crows]
What happened?
A miracle. Aureliano.
God has given you the opportunity
to prove you can be an honorable man
and to be with your family.
Not only that.
but Renata's coming home soon.
[bell rings]
- [machete's slicing]
- [men's shouting indistinctly]
[carriage approaching]
[indistinct shouting continues]
[José Arcadio II] Hey. guys!
These are ready to go.
Get liquid from that barrel.
There's more coming. Come on. come on!
Sir.
- Take this. Come on.
- Okay.
[grunts] You got it.
[man] Spray the ones over there
so we can get this done sooner.
Here you go. That's it.
Hey. give me a hand.
Let's go. let's go. let's go!
Come on. fellas. come on!
[man] Here.
What is that thing?
It's a chemical they sent
to help save our crops.
We have to kill the bugs
that are ruining our bananas.
[narrator] Lorenzo Gavilán.
a colonel of the Mexican Revolution
exiled in Macondo.
who claimed to have witnessed
the heroism of his comrade. Artemio Cruz.
had come. like many others.
to work on the banana plantation.
One last thing. José Arcadio.
What. Gavilán. what?
The toilet they brought at Christmas…
is falling apart.
It might be the latest Yankee invention.
but over here.
we need some efficient
and dignified latrines. don't you think?
- I'll talk to Mr. Brown.
- [train whistle blaring]
[indistinct chattering]
[street vendor] Empanadas! Fresh and hot!
[man] It's the last train to town.
[train whistle blaring]
[conductor] Macondo!
Macondo!
Next stop. Fundación!
[whistle blows]
[conductor] Train leaves for Fundación
in ten minutes!
[both laughing]
Your mother doesn't get a hello?
Mother Superior sends her best.
When did my girl get so big. huh?
[laughs]
- Well. right back at ya!
- [both laugh]
Renata!
Come on. let's go home now.
Welcome home. sweetheart.
You look beautiful.
- Beautiful.
- You too. Papa.
[both laughing]
Mama Úrsula asks me every day.
"How's Meme?"
- "How's Mem--"
- Aureliano Buendía.
Mr. Brown.
Coming back from. uh. the capital?
I didn't see you in first class.
Mm. no. It was just my daughter. Meme.
Uh. Renata.
Well. pleased to meet you. señorita.
This is my daughter. Patricia.
Nice to meet you. I'm Meme.
Be polite.
Hi.
[Mr. Brown]
Visiting family in the capital?
No. She was studying.
My daughter is one of
the best clavichordists in the country.
[Patricia chuckles]
Well. why don't you come and play for us
at the company club sometime?
- We'd be delighted to have you.
- Sure.
- She'd love--
- We'll have to think about it.
If you'll please excuse us.
we're expected for lunch.
Mr. Brown.
Señorita.
[Mr. Brown] Goodbye.
- Nice to meet you!
- Renata.
That's enough.
[melodic clavichord music playing]
[narrator] Although Meme hadn't really
found her true vocation.
she had still earned the highest grades…
Give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us our trespasses.
as we forgive those
who trespass against us.
…largely due to her unwavering discipline
to avoid upsetting her mother.
Our Father. who art in heaven.
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come.
Thy will be done on earth
as it is in heaven.
[Aureliano II snoring]
[snorts]
[snoring continues]
[narrator] She endured performances
with the same stoicism
with which she devoted herself
to her studies.
[music stops]
[narrator] That was the price
of her freedom.
[door opens]
[retches]
[coughing]
[Aureliano II] Are you all right?
We have to cancel the recital
at the plantation.
- Fernanda. we talked about this already.
- I said no. Aureliano.
I said no.
- I'm pregnant.
- Mm. Hmm?
[intriguing music playing]
I'm not leaving this bed.
and you're not going to convince me
to let Renata go by herself.
All you need to do. Fernanda.
is bring this child into the Buendía home
safe and sound.
I'll take care of Meme.
Mama Úrsula!
- Aurelia--
- I'm going to be a father!
[retching]
[coughs. vomits]
[intriguing music continues]
[Fernanda] Swear it on the Virgin.
Christ. and the Holy Spirit. Renata.
Decency. modesty. fear of God.
for Christ. the Virgin.
and the Holy Spirit.
And what else?
What else?
I promise I'll be back
before it gets dark.
By our Lord and Savior.
Amen.
That's enough. Fernanda.
She'll be fine as long as
she doesn't come back a Protestant.
Go on. child. You go and have fun.
[both chuckle]
Enjoy yourself.
[train whistle blaring]
[soothing music playing]
[young Meme] Uncle.
do you live here too?
No. it's only company executives
and their families.
They're all American.
Are they your friends?
I mean. Mr. Brown has been
very good to me.
- This is where the recital's at?
- Uh-huh.
[young Meme] Patricia!
[Patricia in Spanish]
Your name was Renata. right?
[in English] Meme.
But hey. please don't feel like
you need to talk to me in Spanish
'cause we're in Macondo.
I. uh. I can speak English.
Very well. Meme.
Did you bring your bathing suit?
No.
May I borrow one?
Of course.
Give her your bathing suit.
Okay.
Come on.
[José Arcadio II] Hey!
Where should I put the clavichord?
We have more staff
in the grand hall. José Arcadio.
You know that!
Meme!
I'll pick you up later this evening!
Okay!
[jazz music playing]
[jazz music continues]
[Patricia] Meme.
[chuckles]
[music fades]
[clavichord music playing]
[dramatic note plays]
[dramatic clavichord music playing]
[music stops]
She is excellent.
[dramatic clavichord music resumes]
[music stops]
[all clapping]
- [jazz music playing]
- [young Meme] Wait!
Patricia.
Patricia. No.
[both laughing]
[Patricia laughs]
[groans]
Where were you all this time?
- In a convent.
- [laughs]
[both laughing]
Come on. there's something
I wanna show you.
No.
- Meme! Come on.
- No. my uncle will be here any second.
Meme! Are you still a nun or what?
I will take you home later.
[both laughing]
- [bottle shatters]
- [gasps]
[both laughing]
[Patricia] Sh.
- [Patricia clears throat]
- [indistinct chattering]
[Patricia] Is Néstor around?
No. miss. I'm sorry.
I think he went out with your father.
Let's go. Come on.
[man] What exactly do you need?
Hey. can you drive us
around the plantation?
[intriguing music playing]
[man 2] No. that's not gonna work.
This is the spare.
[narrator] His name
was Mauricio Babilonia.
You got the key?
[narrator] He was born and raised
in Macondo
and was an apprentice mechanic
in the banana company's workshops.
Okay. Let's go.
[music fades]
Meme!
[shouting. laughing]
[Patricia continues shouting. laughing]
Do you wanna learn?
Yes. you have to. Meme. Pull over here.
Stop. stop. stop. Stop!
[young Meme] What do I do?
[Mauricio] Don't let go until I tell you.
Then you can start
releasing the pedal slowly.
Then at the same time.
you gotta press that pedal
with your other foot.
You got that?
Like a piano.
[Mauricio chuckles]
Yeah! Come on. you can do it.
Come on. come on!
All right. well.
I've told you everything you need to know.
So hit it. Come on.
- All right! Come on! Come on. go!
- Go ahead. Miss Know-it-all.
- [screams]
- Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
- Slowly! Hey! Hey!
- [laughing]
[lively percussive music playing]
Now press the pedal again.
Hey. step on the pedal.
Uh-huh.
Let go. let go!
Meme! Slow down. woman! Jesus!
[Patricia] Faster. faster. faster!
[Mauricio] Hey. slow down!
Slow down. stop!
[girls laughing]
Slowly. slowly.
Did I scare ya?
Come on. I'm not scared.
[Patricia] Come on. faster!
[laughs. screams]
[music stops]
We gotta start earlier tomorrow.
We didn't get through
all of today's batches.
[indistinct chattering]
- What's the matter with you?
- [man sighs]
My whole entire body's itching. Here.
It's this stuff
they're having us spray. boss.
Anybody else itching?
[man 2] Hey. boys. show him.
[man 3] Yeah. me too. boss.
Look.
[Gavilán] It's not just us.
The women and children
have also been getting sick.
What did they say at the health center?
- [somber music playing]
- [chuckles]
[scoffs] "The health center."
[narrator] The company's physicians
never examined the sick.
Instead. a nurse would place
vibrant-turquoise-colored pills
on their tongues.
regardless if they had malaria.
gonorrhea. or constipation.
It was such a common treatment
that children would stand in line
several times.
And instead of swallowing them.
they'd take the pills home
and use them as markers
in games of lottery.
Hey.
[José Arcadio II] What do the doctors say
about us using the chemicals?
[Gavilán] That it's not the cause.
And what's the problem with the toilet?
[distant coughing]
[indistinct chattering]
[flies buzzing]
[coughing]
It's not just the chemicals
that are making us sick. my friend.
[coughs]
[music stops]
[jazz music playing in distance]
[knocking at door]
Good evening. Cesa.
Good evening. José Arcadio.
- How are you?
- I'm fine. How are you?
I need to speak to Mr. Brown.
[Cesa] I'll get him for you.
He's a little busy. Come in.
[laughter]
[indistinct chattering]
[Cesa] Sir. you have a visitor.
[Mr. Brown] Give me a moment. everybody.
I'll be right back.
- José Arcadio.
- Mr. Brown.
- Buenas noches.
- Evening. sir.
Mm. My daughter. Patricia.
already took your niece home.
She's very talented.
Give my congratulations to your brother.
Seriously. she was great.
I appreciate that. Mr. Brown.
but that's not why I'm here.
Not sure if you recall before you left.
I mentioned us having to solve a problem
with the barracks.
Sure. we'll talk about it tomorrow.
I'm busy.
No.
I need to speak to you right now.
Right. what's the matter?
Half of my day workers are sick
and bedridden.
The living and working conditions
are terrible.
Which is why we gave 'em a health center.
One that doesn't work.
And I'm sorry. sir. but those medics
are not qualified for the job.
They can go
to Aracataca or Fundación. then.
What's the big deal?
Sure. but we also have a problem
with the toilet.
- The whole thing.
- Enough. foreman.
Tomorrow.
- Good evening.
Sorry for the intrusion.
[Mr. Brown in Spanish]
Another whiskey. please.
[in English] How's everybody else doing
on drinks?
[narrator] Meme never forgot that day.
She had spent exhilarating hours
with Patricia.
shedding tears of laughter and fear.
And beyond the crisis.
she had found a strange kind of bravery
she had once needed
to run away from school.
Meme. do you promise
you'll come back soon and visit me?
I promise. but you gotta get out of here.
[vehicle drives away]
Who drove you home?
Patricia and her driver.
[whispers] I forbid you
from ever going back.
But why?
You will not speak to me
like that. Renata.
In fact…
you're forbidden
from leaving this house alone.
Forbidden!
[young Meme grunts]
[young Meme crying]
It's just your mom's pregnancy.
That's why she's like this.
[Meme continues crying]
How about a picture this weekend.
you and me?
[footsteps approaching]
You'd really take me to the pictures?
[Meme sniffles]
[in Spanish]
♪ But he didn't invite the toad ♪
♪ Because he told everything ♪
♪ I saw the cat with the pig ♪
♪ The dog. the rooster. and the cat ♪
♪ Talking for a long time
In fluent Italian ♪
♪ I saw the chick and his brother
Speaking German ♪
♪ And I saw the hawk
Acting all high and mighty ♪
♪ Invite them in Chinese
To buy soda and bread ♪
♪ The day the cockroach
Fell in love with the centipede ♪
♪ The butterfly shouted
She's crazy. she's drunk ♪
♪ She's a spotless female ♪
♪ She said with her face down ♪
♪ He'll never work
Shouted the cricket loudly ♪
♪ Because he's a simple guy ♪
♪ And doesn't like disorder ♪
[in English] You have a glow about you
since your daughter returned.
I was afraid that you'd be mad at me.
[chuckles] Why would I be mad?
You were half-dead
when you left that night.
[both laughing]
[Aureliano II sighs]
[Aureliano II groans]
Heard the big news.
I'm sure you must be happy.
I can't imagine one more day
without seeing you.
[accordion music playing]
But I also can't abandon my unborn child.
or Meme right now.
[Petra chuckles]
[music stops]
[man] You owe us money. We were sick.
[Gavilán] We just wanna talk. Mr. Brown.
We can't do anything!
- We just wanna talk to Mr. Brown.
- [man] He's trying to screw us!
- We wanna speak to him!
- [Gavilán] Get off of me!
[José Arcadio II] Hey. hey!
What the hell's going on?
Yeah! Enough! What is going on?
What do you mean "what's going on"?
They're saying they won't pay us
since we went to a doctor.
[Gavilán] This is messed up. man.
This is abuse of power!
[guard] Yeah. yeah. Keep moving. Let's go.
[man 3] You don't make the law
around here!
[guard] Hey. calm down.
Mr. Buendía!
[José Arcadio II]
Why haven't the workers been paid?
Did you forget to knock?
They went to see a doctor
with your authorization.
And who told them
that they were getting paid
for going to see a doctor. buddy?
[snickers]
Don't act so surprised. all right?
Our company
is not a charitable foundation.
If you don't work. you don't get paid.
Is that why you had them
kicked out of the building?
- All they wanted was to have a word.
- They're not here to talk.
They're here to cut bananas.
for God's sake!
Jesus Christ!
[Mr. Brown sighs]
This is unlike you. José Arcadio Buendía.
Or are you letting them feed your head
with their silly communist ideas?
That it?
Huh?
Just get them under control. foreman.
You don't really want to be against me.
[insects chittering]
[José Arcadio II]
I know this isn't enough.
but the only thing that I can do for now…
is give everyone twice as many vouchers
so you can use them
at the town commissary.
Listen. I know you mean well.
José Arcadio…
but I'm afraid you still have
much to understand in this life
if you really believe that our dignity
is only worth some Virginia ham.
Gavilán.
I'm on your side.
[somber music playing]
Then show us.
[indistinct chattering]
IN MEMORY OF COLONEL AURELIANO BUENDÍA
[music fades]
[melodic music playing]
[indistinct chattering]
THEY LEFT THE DOLL.
IT WAS SO BEAUTIFUL I WANTED TO STEAL IT…
[man] Corn. fresh corn.
[narrator] The first Saturday
she went to the cinema with her father.
Meme saw Mauricio Babilonia again.
And the anxiety was so overwhelming
that she had to make a tremendous effort
to keep anyone from noticing
that her heart was leaping
out of her mouth.
- Poor girl.
- Mm-hmm.
[Aureliano II] What a great movie.
I thought it was beautiful.
[Mauricio] Good evening. Mr. Buendía.
Well. well Mr. Babilonia.
- How's work treating you these days?
- It's nonstop. You know how it is.
At least you make enough money
for a night out like this.
- Hmm.
- Have you met my daughter?
No.
It's nice to meet you. miss.
[mysterious music playing]
[narrator] Bewildered by a strange mixture
of pleasure and rage…
she gave him her hand…
and almost instantly regretted
the impulse.
though the regret
quickly turned into a cruel satisfaction…
It was a pleasure to see you.
- Good night. Babilonia.
- Evening.
…as she realized that his hand. too.
was sweaty and cold as ice.
[music fades]
[Amaranta snoring]
[indistinct chattering]
[car horn honks]
[Patricia] Meme!
[Patricia laughs]
You can't wear that to the party. Meme!
[both laugh]
Catch!
Ready?
[both laughing]
[Patricia] Get out of here! Whoo!
- It's pretty. right?
- [young Meme] So pretty!
[percussive music playing]
[music stops]
[man] One. two… A one. two. three. four!
- [crowd whooping]
- [lively jazz music playing]
[gasps]
You're amazing!
[music continues in distance]
Re… Renata.
[screams. laughs]
[gasps]
[mysterious music playing]
[lively jazz music resumes]
Whoa!
[lively jazz music continues in distance]
[panting]
[gasps]
[music stops]
[breathing heavily]
[clattering]
[young Meme] Hello.
Hey.
Patricia said you got new cars.
and. um. I…
Well. I wanted to see 'em.
That's some story.
But don't worry.
It's not the first time
a woman's gone crazy for a man.
Don't be ridiculous. Babilonia.
A guy like you would be lucky
to have a woman like me.
[intriguing music playing]
[young Meme gasps]
[narrator] The first time they were alone.
he mercilessly dragged her
into an animalistic state
that left her exhausted.
[moaning]
It took Meme some time to understand
that this. too. was a form of tenderness.
It was then when she lost her composure.
Let me go.
[music stops]
[Mauricio chuckles]
[sighs]
[chuckles]
- [lively music playing]
- [man] Come on. Let's go. Let's play.
Let's play.
[fireworks exploding]
[man] Bring that bottle over here.
Are you finishing it on your own?
[indistinct chattering]
[lively music continues]
You are Aureliano's daughter.
I recognize a Buendía a mile away.
Especially when they're deep in love.
You don't have anyone
to talk to about it. do you?
You're welcome to come over anytime.
When you're ready.
just ask anyone where Pilar lives.
Everyone here knows.
I'll be waiting for you.
[lively music continues]
[Aureliano II] Meme!
[both] Let me explain.
[Aureliano II laughs]
[both laughing]
So I'm guessing she's why you and Mom
are always fighting.
Petra.
Meme.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah. you too.
No.
[both laughing]
[lively music continues in distance]
[Aureliano II]
Love is complicated. sweetheart.
[fireworks explode in distance]
I swear no one will ever find out
you were here tonight.
but you have to promise to tell me
when you fall in love with someone.
But how do you know
when you've fallen in love?
Oh. that's easy.
You feel like the earth is shaking.
Promise me.
[knocking at door]
Wait. careful. Meme.
Careful you don't prick yourself.
[both laugh]
- [Sofía] Good morning.
- [Mauricio] Good morning.
[Sofía] What can I do for you?
[Mauricio] This is a gift
from Miss Patricia Brown to Miss Renata.
Look at how beautifully
these have bloomed.
- [Sofía] You have a good day now.
- [Mauricio] Thank you.
[Sofía] Hmm. never seen him before.
[intriguing music playing]
[Sofía] Meme.
Here.
Someone sent this.
What's gotten into you?
[Úrsula] She is her father's daughter.
[chuckles]
Renata. what are you…
[panting]
[chuckles]
- [music stops]
- [machete slices]
[man 1] Hey. Juan.
hand me the ladder. will you?
[indistinct chattering]
[man 2] You get that side.
I'll get the other.
[ominous music playing]
[car horn honks]
[indistinct shouting]
[music fades]
Everything all right?
You tell me. Is everything all right here?
It sure is. yeah.
[mysterious music playing]
TOMORROW AT 7 PM AT THE MATRON'S PLACE
[music fades]
Here.
- This will do you well.
- Mm.
[Úrsula chuckles]
Thanks.
Renata.
I'm still waiting for an apology.
I don't feel that well. Mama.
[Úrsula] Fernanda.
this is not just about Meme.
There comes a day in every mother's life
when we realize there's no way for us
to control our children.
Don't take this the wrong way
'cause I only say this with love.
The more that you try
to change your daughter.
the farther she will drift away.
Here. Put those on the table.
[indistinct chattering]
Hey. do me a favor.
Tell me where I can find Pilar Ternera.
Sure. that red house over there.
Thanks.
I don't need to read your cards
to know what's going on.
You have the same look
the colonel had when he confessed to me
that he'd fallen in love
with the wrong person.
Do you believe it's worth the risk?
True love is always worth it.
But the issue is you must try first
to know if it is true or not.
[suspenseful music playing]
Come on.
[narrator] Pilar Ternera
not only dispelled her fears.
but also offered Meme the old canvas bed
where she conceived Arcadio.
Meme's grandfather.
and where she later conceived
Aureliano José.
[Mauricio] Give me two.
[lively jazz music playing]
Thanks.
[man] Next? How many tickets do you want?
[Pilar] Babilonia?
Mauricio Babilonia?
- Yes.
- Come on.
Come with me.
Trust me. It is in your best interest.
[poignant music playing]
[Renata breathes shakily]
[melancholy French music playing]
[woman moaning]
[moaning continues]
One complaint from us.
one single complaint.
and now we've got guards watching us
every time we take a piss.
Why do we have to hide and sneak around
like we're a bunch of criminals?
I helped establish this thing.
José Arcadio.
but this is messed up. all right?
They just keep asking for more.
I'll fund something else
if things don't change.
Yeah. me too.
Even if I have to leave Macondo.
This can't go on any longer.
And it shouldn't have to either.
[Gavilán]So how long do we put up with it?
Huh?
How much longer until we can show
these motherfucking gringos
that. without us.
they have nothing?
Listen. Buendía. We're moving forward
on our own. with or without you.
We need to know whose side you're on.
Yeah. he's right.
You need to think about it. boss.
[music stops]
Renata.
Renata?
Are you all right?
[tense music playing]
[breathing shakily]
- [young Meme laughs]
- Come on. slowpoke. faster!
Faster. huh?
[both laughing]
Keep up! [laughs]
[young Meme laughing]
I'm gonna beat you!
[Mauricio screams. laughs]
[indistinct chattering]
Thank you for coming. José Arcadio.
Take care. all right? And think about it.
Yes.
See you later.
- See you.
- Thanks. man.
Good luck. foreman.
[tense music continues]
Where are you off to. sister?
[melodic acoustic guitar music playing]
[tense music playing]
[laughter]
[lively music playing]
[dark ethereal music playing]
[narrator] From the shadows
of the box seats.
Fernanda recognized her daughter.
[dark ethereal music continues]
[man 1] So what do you think?
[Gavilán] I don't think
we can count on him right now.
but we can't wait for him either.
Come on. boys. let's g--
Renata.
[narrator] Although the satisfaction
she got from being right
prevented her from seeing the man
her daughter was kissing.
amid the jeering.
Fernanda caught the tremor in his voice.
[Mauricio] I'm sorry. my love.
[audience whistling. shouting]
[young Meme gasps]
[dark ethereal music continues]
[people murmuring]
[grunting]
[train tracks rattling]
[music fades]
[somber music playing]
[mysterious ethereal music playing]
[music fades]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm